hello everyone Tamara's 1345 here with a
very special video today so as some of
you may remember a while back I made a
video about what if saga can Bobby will
pick cities and ever since then I have
been getting a lot of a quest about can
I show them how I made a lock tables my
father like how the did you make
that like did you draw them yourself no
I didn't that is a very easy answer to
your questions there is this
thing called pixie see maker that you
can find on the internet I mean just
google that so I thought hey while
I'm taking a I will show you how to
make it let us begin so these do not
distract us I will go ahead and move
them off screen I think it would be easy
to start off with sog the Hedgehog
because most of you know more about him
remember Sonic is why he is not black he
has black eyes do not give him grain or
it will be modern sock and if we don't
want that I do not worry making
sock and Bobby this is actually rather
easy the creator of this pic CC maker is
a really big fan of mine and a fan saw
kind in general so he put a ton of stuff
that I'll reference a not sock on the
ground we will begin first give Sonic
blue hands now that is not the right
shade of blue for Sonic so just get this
one it's really better than nothing
moving on to the next step as you can
see there is not a mohawk for Sonic
although that can easily be bypassed as
you will see in a minute just pick this
hairstyle and when you are done you're
ready to move on to the next step as you
can see this is where we will make the
Mohawk just free
take this flip it around boom can
you find the mohawk I can as you
can see we have just gave Sonic his
mohawk now if we want we can stop right
here because Sonic is basically done but
if you want to move on go on to the next
step now just move on SOG does not wash
it but he does however what pans give
him his pants do not pick that shade
pick this one already is looking good so
as I told you the creator of this is at
a really big fan of my like you cannot
make this up give him his vest and
then if you are done with that y'all
ready to move on to the next step boom
Sonic has a red belt so go ahead and
give that to him Sonic is basically done
though there was one thing left we must
give him his pixi wings and there you go
you have just made Sonic the Hedgehog as
you can see we are ready to move on to
bottle-feed be sure to change your skin
color too beautiful give him black out
and have him smile because he is happy
to be with his lover if in beautiful
beautiful blonde hair give him his
golden past do not get yellow there are
many times do not be tracked you see
this hair back here this is the hell we
will be using but do not pick it yet we
will make it beautiful give him his long
beautiful hair
mmm move on to the next step now you do
not need to do anything here but when I
want to have fun on pigs AC maker I'll
do this oh yes make Bobby's help
beautiful move on boom Bobby unlike
Sonic was close go remember when we made
Bobby's pads go go back to the beginning
and switch them to brown you see what
that done I did go back to where we were
you see this Bobby was a golden cave
boom move on to the next step Bobby does
not wear much here but he does now give
him this then you're done moving on
be sure to give him his beautiful golden
wings and his sparkles sparkles is a
must give him his ball of light like his
touching song balls give him roses that
he's gone moving on no you're basically
done but if you want to have fun you
from sparkle when I whenever I come on
pixie ce mec I like to imagine Bobby
gets his power from the Sun because he
is a pixel so unlike Sonic he is far
more powerful now that we all don't obby
click view you can now see the two
Pixies you have made what is really cool
as website you can make a scene as the
Taj as they are now having a tea powder
day and remember the pics is from the
beginning bring them up
look at that you can that you can have
you can make multiple copies of a pic
say Bobby and sock I'm now having a
double days